// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "In final exam of class IX there are 130 students 20 % students failed. How many students passed to class X?",
    answer: "104",
    options: ["105", "112", "104", "111"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "Sanjay gets 72 % marks in examinations. If these are 864 marks, find the maximum marks.",
    answer: "1200",
    options: ["1050", "860", "1200", "1300"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "In a college of 1335 students, 60 % are boys. Find the number of girls and number of boys in the college?",
    answer: "534,801",
    options: ["924,221", "691,404", "691,405", "534,801"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Find the increase value if 450 is increased by 90 %.",
    answer: "855",
    options: ["910", "855", "313", "545"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "The cost of a stencil is decreased by 30%. If the original cost is $140, find the decrease cost.",
    answer: "98",
    options: ["98", "100", "87", "101"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question:
      "There are 2 positive integers x and y. What is the probability that x + y is odd?",
    answer: "1/2",
    options: ["1/2", "3/2", "2/5", "8/3"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "What is the harmonic mean of two numbers whose geometric mean and arithmetic mean are 6 and 12, respectively?",
    answer: "3",
    options: ["5", "3", "8", "1"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "If GM = 12 and HM = 7.2, then what will be the value of AM?",
    answer: "20",
    options: ["22", "18", "34", "16"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the sum of all the odd numbers up to 100?",
    answer: "2500",
    options: ["2200", "2100", "1800", "2500"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the maximum sum of the series 60, 56, 52, 48, ...?",
    answer: "480",
    options: ["500", "513", "699", "480"],
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  // {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "option 3",
  //   options: ["Option 1", "option 2", "option 3", "option 4"],
  // },
];
